Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors but lower
in calories and higher in protein.
This is mint chocolate cookie. Let me
show you how to make it. If there's one
recipe that tastes as good as the real
thing, it's this one. It's crazy.
>> And I know I say this about basically
every recipe I post, but this is 100% in
my top five recipes of all time. And
that's probably biased because mint Oreo
is in my top five ice cream flavors of
all time. Honestly, now that I'm
thinking about it, if you put Oreos in
any ice cream flavor, it somehow finds
its way into my top 10 flavors. And now
we're 40 seconds into the video and I
haven't explained the recipe at all. So,
I'll just give you a few tips. The full
written recipe will be down below in the
description. Biggest thing with this
recipe is the peppermint extract. It has
to be peppermint extract. It cannot be
mint extract. I realize it seems like
they're the same thing. They are not.
So, be careful with that. And also, be
careful adding it in. Eighth of a
teaspoon, no more, no less. Five to six
drops. That's all you need. Otherwise,
it's going to taste like toothpaste.